A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1967-1968
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1967-1968
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.711
This collection consists of 46,200 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 26 July 1971.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
Contents List
- General Files, 1967-1968
  - "A - Al" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Academic Deans 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Academic Freedom and Tenure 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Adams Papers 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Admissions, general 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Admissions, applicants 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Admissions Reports 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Air Force Academy 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Air Force Academy - Board of Visitors 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Air Force and Air Force ROTC 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni - Distinguished Professor Award 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Day 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Lynchburg 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Mary Washington College 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Fund - University of Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni - Medical 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni - Richmond 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni News 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Recognition 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Speeches 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Applications 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Architecture - General 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Architecture - Personnel 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Army - General 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Army - ROTC 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Judge Advocate General's (J. A. G.) School of the Army 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Art 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Art Commission 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Astronomy 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - general 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Invitations to games 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - personnel 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - ACC 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - finances 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - football 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - Football: Buffalo game, 30 September 1967 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - Football: Duke game, 14 October 1967 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - Football: V. M. I. game, 28 October 1967 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - Football: Commonwealth Day, 28 October 1967 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - Football: N. C. State game, 4 November 1967 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - Football: North Carolina Game, 11 November 1967 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Athletics - NCAA 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Atomic Energy Commission 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Audit Reports 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - "B - Bm" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - "Bn - Bz" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Berkeley, Francis L. Jr. 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Biology - general 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Biology - Blandy Farm 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Biology - Mountain Lake 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Bond Issue 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Budget - Director's Office 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Budget - Capital Outlay 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Budget - Miscellaneous Information 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Budget - "To be held in budget file" 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Budget - Requests 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds - general 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds - Progress reports 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Building Program [see also by department involved] 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Bureau of Population and Economic Research 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Bursar [info. re: tuition, fees, benefits] 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - "C - Ck" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - "Cl - Cz" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Calendar of Events 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Catholic Center 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Cavalier Daily 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Center for Advanced Studies 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Chemistry - general 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Civil Defense 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Civil Rights 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Clinch Valley College - general 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Clinch Valley College - Building Program 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Clinch Valley College - personnel 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - College Entrance Examination Board [see also Admissions] 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Commerce - general 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committees - Administrative 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - AD HOC Committee - Historical Archives Research Institute 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - AD HOC Committee - Transfer Students from New Community Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Architectural Advisory 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Athletic Advisory Council 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Blandy Farm 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Calendar and Scheduling 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Catalogues 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Chapel 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Communications 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Computer Science 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Danforth Fellowships 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Fellowships 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Foreign Students 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Fraternities 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Fulbright Grants 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Graphics 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Housing 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Institutional Analysis 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Lectures (Page-Barbour) 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Library 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Master Plan 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Medical Affairs Policy 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Names 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - National Medal of Science 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Committee - Objects of Art 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Processions 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Public Occasions 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Radiation Safety 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Registration 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Research and Sponsored Programs 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Research in the Humanities 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Rhodes Scholarships 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - ROTC Affairs 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Schedule of Events 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans, Employment Fellows 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Security and General Safety 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Student Activities 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Student Health 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Summer Grants 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - University Committee on Students 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - University Press 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - University Union 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Committee - Virginia Status of University Students 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Admissions, Women, College of Arts and Sciences 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Central Utilities, planning 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Departmental Grants 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Dean and Associate Dean of the University 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Education, Dean of 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Dean of: Schaller, Howard; Bailey, Martin J.; Swanson, Carl; Kinsman, Robert Starr 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Faculty Handbook 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - George Mason College, Arts and Sciences Building 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - George Mason College, Master Plan 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Heating Plant 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - International Studies and Research 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Law School, Dean of 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Law and Graduate Business at Copely Hill 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Medical Communications Building (Med. Library) 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Orientation 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Reactor Safety 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Social Needs and Facilities 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Student Health Insurance 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Training Center for teachers of handicapped 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Trees 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - University Committee on Committees 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Special Committee - Washington Papers 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Comptroller 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Computer Center 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Council of Presidents 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - "D" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Dali Jewels 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Darlington School - Board of Trustees 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Degrees 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Demonstrations - Letters, "A - I" 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - Demonstrations - Letters, "J - Z" 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - Development and Public Affairs 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - East-West Highway 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Economics 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Education - general 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Education - personnel 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Educational T. V. 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Endowment Fund and Annual Trust Report 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Engineering - general 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Engineering - personnel 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Division of State Office 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - English 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Enrollment [see also Registrar] 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty - general 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Tenure 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Tenure - Five Year Staffing 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Academic 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - general 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committees of 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "A - M" 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "N - Z" 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Faculty Orientation and Reception 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - DuPont Regional 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Hoxton 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Finals 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Financial Aid to Students, Office of 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Ford Foundation 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - Foreign Student Advisor 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - Founder's Day 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - General Assembly 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - General Assembly - Special 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - General Studies - general 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Central Virginia Center 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch, personnel 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Hampton Roads 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Hampton Roads, Personnel 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg Branch 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch, personnel 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Richmond Center personnel 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Center 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Center, personnel 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - Geography 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - Geology 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - George Mason College - general 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - George Mason College - Building program 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - George Mason College - Monthly Reports 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - George Mason College - Personnel 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - George Mason College - Recommendations to Director 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - George Mason College - Foundation, Inc. 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - Germanic and Slavic Languages 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - Gifts and Grants 1967-1968 (Box 26)
  - Gifts and Grants (4) 1967-1968 (Box 26)
  - Gifts and Grants (3) 1967-1968 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants (2) 1967-1968 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants (1) 1967-1968 (Box 28)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1967-1968 (Box 28)
  - Governor's Office 1967-1968 (Box 28)
  - Governor's Visit (1967) with Budget Advisory Board and HUD Title VIII 1967-1968 (Box 28)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Graduate Programs 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Graduate - Three Years Master's Program 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Graduate Business - sponsors 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Graduate Degree Programs in Tidewater Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - Grants-in-Aid for Culturally Deprived Students 1967-1968 (Box 30)
  - Graphics Department 1967-1968 (Box 30)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1967-1968 (Box 30)
  - "H" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 30)
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 - Title I 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 - Title II 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 - Title III 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 - Title IV 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 - Title V 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 - Title VI 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education Study Commission 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Highway Department 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - History 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Honor System and Honor Committee 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Honors Program 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Housing 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Information Services (and pamphlets re: U.Va.) 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Institute of Government 1967-1968 (Box 33)
  - Institute of International Education 1967-1968 (Box 33)
  - Institutional Analysis, Office of 1967-1968 (Box 33)
  - Invitations - "A" 1967-1968 (Box 33)
  - Invitations - "B" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "C" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "D" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "E" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "F" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "G" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "H" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "I" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "J" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "K" 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Invitations - "L" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "M" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "N" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "O" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "P" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "Q" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "R" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "S" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "T" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "U" 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Invitations - "V" 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Invitations - "W" 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Invitations - "X" 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Invitations - "Y" 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Invitations - "Z" 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Thomas Jefferson Center 1967-1968 (Box 36)
  - Jefferson Society 1967-1968 (Box 37)
  - Jefferson - Papers 1967-1968 (Box 37)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 37)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 37)
  - Law - general 1967-1968 (Box 38)
  - Law - personnel 1967-1968 (Box 38)
  - Lectures 1967-1968 (Box 38)
  - Lectures - Page-Barbour and Richard 1967-1968 (Box 38)
  - Legal - general 1967-1968 (Box 39)
  - Legal - estates, deeds 1967-1968 (Box 39)
  - Library - general 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - Library - Allocations 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - Library - Annual Report 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - Library - Board of Alderman 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - McGregor Fund [see also Library] 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - McConnel Award (empty) 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - McIntire Fund 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - McIntire Undergraduate School of Commerce 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - "M" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 41)
  - Mariner's Museum 1967-1968 (Box 41)
  - Mariner's Museum Reports 1967-1968 (Box 42)
  - Marine Sciences 1967-1968 (Box 42)
  - Markle Foundation 1967-1968 (Box 42)
  - Mary Washington College Bulletins 1967-1968 (Box 42)
  - Mary Washington College - general 1967-1968 (Box 43)
  - Mary Washington College - Building Program 1967-1968 (Box 43)
  - Mary Washington College - Financial 1967-1968 (Box 43)
  - Mary Washington College - personnel 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Master Site Plan (empty) 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Mathematics 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center - general 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center - Finances 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center - Hospital 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center - Medical School 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center - Medical School Personnel 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center - Monthly Statistical Reports 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - Medical Center - Nursing 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - Medical Center - Nursing, personnel 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - Medical Center - Operating Budget and Reports 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - Medical Center - Reports on Current Operations 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - James Monroe Memorial Library and Museum 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - Monroe Papers 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - Music 1967-1968 (Box 45)
  - "N" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - NASA [see also VARC] 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) 2 1967-1968 (Box 47)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) 1 1967-1968 (Box 47)
  - NASULGC - International Letters 1967-1968 (Box 48)
  - NASULGC - Circular Letters 1967-1968 (Box 48)
  - National Commission on Accrediting 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - National Defense Education Act (Student Loans) 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - National Historical Publications Commission 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - National Medal of Science 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - National Science Foundation - grants 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - National Science Foundation - general and reports 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - National Trust for Historical Preservation 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - Navy - general 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - Navy - ROTC 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - Newcomb Hall 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - Newcomen Society 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - News Letter 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1967-1968 (Box 50)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 51)
  - Office - files 1967-1968 (Box 51)
  - Office - Information 1967-1968 (Box 51)
  - Office - Travel 1967-1968 (Box 51)
  - Office - Invoices 1967-1968 (Box 52)
  - Office General Stores Purchase 1967-1968 (Box 52)
  - Office - Supplies 1967-1968 (Box 52)
  - Office of Institutional Research 1967-1968 (Box 53)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 53)
  - "Pi - Pz" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 54)
  - Personnel 1967-1968 (Box 54)
  - Relative Applications [personnel] 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Personnel Profile 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Personnel Fringe Benefit Sheets 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Personnel Fringe Benefit Sheets 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Personnel Forms and Procedures 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Philosophy 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Physics 1967-1968 (Box 55)
  - Planning Department 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Planning Division - State 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - President's Council 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Project Status Reports 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Provost of the University 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Psychology 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Publications (empty) 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Public Relations [see also University Relations] 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Purchasing 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Questionnaires and Inquiries 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Raven Society 1967-1968 (Box 56)
  - Recommendations 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Registrar 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Registrar - Student Reports 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Rehabilitation Center 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Religion 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Religious Studies 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Research 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Research - Accounting and Control 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - Research - Support Division 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - "S - Sl" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 57)
  - "Sm - Sz" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 58)
  - Salaries 1967-1968 (Box 58)
  - Salaries - Faculty 1967-1968 (Box 58)
  - Scholars in Residence 1967-1968 (Box 58)
  - Security - Department of 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Seely, Charles S. 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Senate, University 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Seven Society 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Sociology and Anthropology 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Southern Fellowships Fund 1967-1968 (Box 60)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1967-1968 (Box 60)
  - Southern University Conference 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - Space Science, Division of 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - Space Utilization (empty) 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - Speeches 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - Speeches - Virginia Retail Merchants Speech 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - Sponsored Programs 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - State Board for Community Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - State Board of Education 1967-1968 (Box 61)
  - State Council on Higher Education and Reports 1967-1968 (Box 62)
  - State Council on Higher Education - Material for 1966-1967 Visit 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - State Department of Education 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - State Technical Services Act (empty) 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - State Universities Association (empty) 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Statistics 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Student Affairs 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Student Council 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Student Council - Minutes (fall 1967) 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Student Counseling Center 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Student Health Department 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Student Legal Forum 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Student Placement 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Summer Session - Finals 1967 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Summer Session 1968 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Traffic Control 1967-1968 (Box 65)
  - Transportation and Safety Center - Proposal 1967-1968 (Box 65)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 65)
  - UNESCO 1967-1968 (Box 66)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture 1967-1968 (Box 66)
  - U. S. Department of Defense 1967-1968 (Box 66)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (H. E. W.) 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - U. S. Department of State 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1967-1968 (Box 67)